ofree.net 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy at ¤ Only Free

Search Freebies,  
Free Stuff &   
Free samples 

Don't forget to bookmark us. (Just press "Control, D")

### Privacy Policy

Ofree.net has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our business in the highest ethical standards and to uphold our promise to the public. However, our policy might change periodically, due to the changes within the environment.

Collecting Data

Ofree.net only collects your email address with your consent to join our Free STUFF & Freebies NEWSLETTER! We will also log your IP in order to prevent abuse. We do not collect any other personal information at this point of time.

Statistical Analysis

Ofree.net does keep track of the pages you surf to and your user preferences, but we only view the data as a form of statistical analysis. We do not view individual surfing styles of users. 

Ofree.net will never disclose your personal information to any third parties.

Disclaimer

Ofree.net is a portal site and has links to external sites. We are not responsible for the contents of these sites. Additionally, we provide descriptions on our site for the convenience of our visitors and these descriptions are written to the best of our knowledge and editorial guidelines. We cannot be held responsible for any of these descriptions. 

Some of the offers listed on our site is not 100% free. You may have to pay Shipping or handling fees or be subjected to other conditions to get some free items. When you are giving out your personal information, please read their privacy policy and all details first. 

For questions regarding this privacy statement or the practises of this site, please contact us by Clicking Here.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.ofree.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

  *   *   *   *   * 

#### Only Free Stuff Newsletter!

Subscribe NOW to Only Free Stuff newsletter for daily updates. 

or 

to  
and Get Only Newest Free Stuff and Free Samples Faster and More Reliably! 

Free Apple iPhone 5

Apple has redefined the mobile world… again 

Only 7 days left for Free Movie Tickets

Summer blockbusters are on their way - watch them for Free 

Do you prefer Nike or Adidas?

Get the shoe brand of your choice Free! Sign-up now! 

Get a New Free Laptop or Tablet Computer – Hurry, Don't Delay

Why pay to upgrade? 

Free Apple iPad 2 and iPhone 4 combo

Own Apple’s fastest, most powerful products yet!
